Guide to the Stanford University, Bing Overseas Studies Program, Records SC0117
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Material, Accession 1985-110
  - Germany: Berlin Budget 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Spain: Salamanca Budget 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Brazil (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Administration Budget 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Britain: Cliveden Budget 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Israel: Haifa Budget 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Italy: Rome Budget 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Germany: Berlin Budget 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Brazil Budget 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Austria: Vienna Budget 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Italy: Florence Budget 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Spain: Salamanca Budget 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - France: Paris Budget 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Israel: Haifa Budget 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Spain: Salamanca Budget 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Germany: Berlin Budget 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Italy: Florence Budget 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - France: Paris Budget 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Administration Budget 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Administration Budget 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Administration Budget 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Administration Budget 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Germany: Bonn Budget 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Peru: Lima Budget 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Africa Proposal 1978 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Italy: Florence Budget 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Italy: Rome Budget 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Austria: Vienna Budget 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - France: Paris Budget 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - France: Tours Budget 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Britain: Cliveden Budget 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Germany: Berlin Budget 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Spain: Salamanca Budget 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Germany: Berlin Budget 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Brazil Budget 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - France: Tours Budget 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Italy: Rome Budget 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Austria: Vienna Budget 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Spain: Salamanca Budget 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Italy: Florence Budget 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - France: Paris Budget 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Britain: Cliveden Budget 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Germany: Berlin Budget 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - France: Tours Budget 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - France: Paris Budget 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Spain: Salamanca Budget 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Italy: Florence Budget 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Israel: Haifa Budget 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Italy: Rome Budget 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Austria: Vienna Budget 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Brazil Budget 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Austria: Vienna Budget 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Britain: Cliveden Budget 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Italy: Rome Budget 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Brazil Budget 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Britain: Cliveden Activation 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Austria: Vienna Budget 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Germany: Beutelsbach Budget 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Germany: Beutelsbach Budget 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Germany: Bonn Budget 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Britain: Cliveden Budget 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - France: Tours Budget 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Italy: Florence Budget 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Italy: Rome Budget 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Paris Budget 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Spain: Salamanca Budget 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Austria: Vienna Budget 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Germany: Beutelsbach Budget 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Germany: Beutelsbach Budget 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Germany: Berlin Budget 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Germany: Bonn Budget 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Britain: Cliveden Budget 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - France: Tours Budget 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Germany: Beutelsbach Budget 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Italy: Florence Budget 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Paris Budget 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Peru: Lima Budget 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Italy: Rome Budget 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Italy: Rome Intercollegiate Center for Classical Studies in Italy General 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Spain: Salamanca Budget 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Peru: Lima General 1974 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - France: Tours Program Alternatives 1976 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - France: Tours Kennedy Library 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Italy: Florence Alternative Housing 1976 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Italy: Florence Activation 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Austria: Vienna La Verne College 1977 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - France: Tours Villa Grandiere Renovation (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Britain: Cliveden Alternative Housing 1976 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Anita Oliver Lunn Fund 1963-1972 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Administration Budget 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Administration Budget 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Britain: Cliveden Personnel 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Britain: Cliveden Budget 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Budget 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - France: Tours Budget 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Germany: Beutelsbach Budget 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Italy: Florence Budget 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Britain: Cliveden Budget 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Austria: Vienna Budget 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Italy: Florence Budget 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - France: Tours Budget 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Germany: Beutelsbach Budget 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Austria Budget 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Britain: Cliveden Budget 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - France: Tours Budget 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Italy: Florence Budget 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Austria: Vienna Budget 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Britain: Cliveden Budget 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - France: Tours Budget 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Germany: Beutelsbach Budget 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Italy: Florence Budget 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Austria: Vienna Budget 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Britain: Cliveden Budget 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - France: Tours Budget 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Italy: Florence Budget 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Additional Material, Accession 1986-039
  - Zuni Pueblo Proposal 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Britain: Cliveden - Oxford Move Faculty Reaction 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Britain: City of Oxford Draft Plan 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Britain: Oxford Development 1976-1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - APC/SOS (Academic Program Committee/Stanford Overseas Studies) Oxford Britain: Oxford Development 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Britain: Oxford Publicity (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Britain: Oxford Facilities Planning 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Britain: Oxford Remodeling 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Britain: Oxford 1983 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Britain: Oxford 1984 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Britain: Oxford Correspondence 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - APC/SOS Oxford Development (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - APC/SOS Documents (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - APC/SOS Minutes 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - APC/SOS Documents 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - APC/SOS Membership 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - APC/SOS Minutes 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - APC/SOS Documents 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - APC/SOS Membership 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - APC/SOS Minutes 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - APC/SOS Documents 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - APC/SOS Minutes 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - CFSP (Committee on Foreign Study Programs) Documents 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - CFSP General 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - CFSP Minutes 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - CFSP Documents 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - CFSP General 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - CFSP Membership 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - CFSP Minutes 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - CFSP Documents 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - CFSP Minutes 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - CFSP General 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - APC/SOS Documents 1980 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - APC/SOS Minutes 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - APC/SOS Year of Initiation Documents 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - APC/SOS Year of Initiation Agendas 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - APC/SOS Year of Initiation Minutes 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - APC/SOS Year of Initiation Charge 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - APC/SOS Year of Initiation Membership 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - APC/SOS 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Academic Council (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - CFSP Documents General 1969-1977 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - CFSP Documents 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Overseas Studies Planning Documents (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Overseas Studies Planning Minutes 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Britain: Oxford Publicity 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Britain: Oxford CFSP, APC/SOS Minutes 1975-1984 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Britain: Oxford Correspondence General 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Britain: Oxford Summary, Planning Committee Appeal (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Britain: Oxford Proposal (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Britain: Oxford Development Contracts, Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Administration - Publicity 1984-1986 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Administration - Publicity 1978-1984 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Academics - ASSU, Course Electives 1977-1985 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Course Abstracts 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Course Abstracts 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Course Abstracts: Cliveden, Beutelsbach, Tours, Florence, Vienna 1970-1973 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Course Abstracts: Cliveden, Beutelsbach, Tours, Florence 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Course Abstracts: Berlin, Cliveden (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Course Abstracts: Lima, Salamanca, Rome, Paris, Cliveden, Tours 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Course Abstracts: Florence, Beutelsbach, Vienna, Berlin 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Course Abstracts: France: Tours, Vienna, Beutelsbach 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Course Abstracts: Florence 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Course Lists: Beutelsbach, Florence (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Course Lists: Vienna, Cliveden, Tours, Beutelsbach, Florence (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Course Abstracts: Berlin, Bonn, Cliveden 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Course Abstracts: Florence, Paris, Rome, Salamanca, Tours, Vienna 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Course Abstracts: Berlin, Cliveden 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Course Abstracts: Florence, Tours, Vienna 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Course Abstracts: 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Course Abstracts: 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Course Abstracts: 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Course Abstracts: 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - CFSP Chairs and Deans Distribution 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - CFSP List Distribution 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - CFSP Meeting Agendas 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - CFSP Minutes Distribution 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - CFSP Meeting Agendas 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Administration Trip Reports 1979-1984 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Administration Policy and Procedures 1973-1983 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Administration Policy and Procedures Financial Aid 1978-1980 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Administration Mills College 1977-1983 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - CFSP Agendas 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - CFSP Ad Hoc Committee 1971 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - CFSP Agendas 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - CFSP Correspondence Distribution 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - CFSP General 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - CFSP Minutes 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - CFSP General 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - CFSP Annual Report 1972 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - CFSP Minutes 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - CFSP Minutes 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - CFSP Academic Appointment Procedures (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - CFSP Special Minutes 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - CFSP Minutes 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - CFSP General 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - CFSP Charge Revision 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Germany: Berlin Krupp Internship Evaluations 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Germany: Berlin Establishment 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Germany: Berlin DAAD Internship 1980-1982 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Germany: Bonn Financial and Physical Operations 1972-1975 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Germany: Berlin Publications, Publicity 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Germany: Berlin Financial and Physical Operations (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Germany: Berlin Grand Opening Reception 1/16/1978 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Britain: Cliveden Financial and Physical Operations 1973-1975 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Britain: Cliveden Tenth Anniversary Photographs 1976 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Britain: Cliveden Publications, Publicity 1981-1983 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Britain: Cliveden Academic Focus Program - Political Economics 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Britain: Cliveden Academic Focus Program - Legal Systems 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Britain: Cliveden Academic Focus Program - Healthcare Delivery 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Britain: Cliveden Academic Focus Program - Healthcare Delivery 1983 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Britain: Cliveden: program from "Ten Nights in a Bar-Room" presented by members of course O.C.B. 129, March 1971 (Box 13, Folder 10.1)
  - CFSP Director Search 1973 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Merryman Commission Report 1972 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Merryman Commission Correspondence (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Merryman Commission Pre-report Correspondence (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Merryman Commission Supporting Documents, History of Overseas Campuses 1972 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Mark Mancall Director Announcements and Correspondence 1973 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Merryman Commission Correspondence (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Academic Focus Program Proposals (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Administration Memoranda 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Merryman Commission Report Responses (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Subcommittee on Austria 1973 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Subcommittee on Germany 1973 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Subcommittee on Britain 1973 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Subcommittee on Italy 1973 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Subcommittee on France 1973 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Supporting Documents 1968 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Germany Development Fundraising 1976-1982 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Financial Reports 1975 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Britain: Cliveden Memoranda, Correspondence 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Britain: Harlaxton Sale 1968-1971 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Germany: Hamburg General (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Britain: Harlaxton, Cliveden Publicity 1965-1971 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Office Expansion, Remodeling, Phones, Equipment, Etc. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Office Expansion, Move to Old Union 1970 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Germany: Beutelsbach Tenth Anniversary 1968 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - CFSP Meetings 1968-1979 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Publicity Stanford Daily (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Publicity 1977-1978 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Publicity General 1960-1970 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Publicity Announcement for Stanford Daily (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Spain: Salamanca Publicity 1969 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Additional Material, Accession 1987-061
  - Britain: Oxford Requisitions Correspondence 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Britain: Oxford Faculty Apartment 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Britain: Oxford Travel and Expenses 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - France: Tours Travel and Expenses 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - France: Tours Requisitions Correspondence 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - France: Tours Room and Board correspondence 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Israel: Haifa Requisitions Correspondence 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Israel: Haifa Transportation 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Alumni Conference 6/1984 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Alumni Conference 9/1984 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Alumni Conference 6/1985 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Italy: Florence Requisitions Correspondence 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - France: Paris Requisitions Correspondence 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Peru: Lima Requisitions Correspondence 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Italy: Rome Budget 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Italy: Rome Institutional Membership 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Italy: Rome Summer Income 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Italy: Rome Requistions correspondence 1984-85 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Spain: Salamanca Requisitions Correspondence 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Faculty Transportation corrrespondence 1985 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Austria Travel and Entertainment - Study tour to Poland 1985 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Krupp Foundation correspondence 1984-85 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Additional Material, Accession 1990-189
  - Curricula General 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Austria: Vienna Correspondence 1984 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Calendar 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Peru: Lima - SOCCIS (Southern California Conference on International Studies) Handbook 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Student Orientation Handbooks 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - France: Tours Student Orientation Handbook Fall 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - France: Tours Student Orientation Handbook Spring 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - France: Tours Student Orientation Handbook Winter 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - France: Tours Student Orientation Handbook Fall 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - France: Tours Student Orientation Handbook Spring 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - France: Tours Student Orientation Handbook Winter 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - France: Tours Student Orientation Handbook Fall 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - France: Tours Student Orientation Handbook 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Stanford-in-France Alumni Publication and Artwork (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - France: Tours Publicity Stanford Observer article (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - France: Tours General 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Latin America General 1970-1980 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - France: Paris Student Orientation Handbook Fall 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - France: Paris Student Orientation Handbook Winter 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Spain: Salamanca Student Orientation Handbook Winter 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Israel: Haifa Student Orientation Handbook 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Nairobi/Lima Student Orientation Handbook 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Britain: Oxford Student Orientation Handbook Fall 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Britain: Oxford Student Orientation Handbook Summer 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Israel: Haifa Student Orientation Handbook 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Britain: Oxford Student Orientation Handbook Spring 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Italy: Florence Student Orientation Handbook Winter 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Germany: Berlin Student Orientation Handbook Spring 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - France: Paris Student Orientation Handbook Winter 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Italy: Florence Student Orientation Handbook Fall 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Africa Program Development 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Israel: Haifa Enrollment/Withdrawals 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Israel: Haifa General Information 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Israel: Haifa Course Abstracts 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Israel: Haifa Student Concerns 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Israel: Haifa Student Concerns 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Israel: Haifa Student Concerns 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Israel: Haifa Transportation 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Israel: Haifa Housing 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Israel: Haifa Telephone Messages 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Israel: Haifa Hebrew Instructor Candidates 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Israel: Haifa Hebrew Instructor 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Israel: Haifa Course Abstracts 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Israel: Haifa Internships 1986 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Israel: Haifa Calendar/Schedules 1981-1985 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Israel: Haifa Contacts 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Israel: Haifa Field Trips 1984 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Israel: Haifa Establishment, Policy and Procedure 1978-1982 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Israel: Haifa Fundraising 1974-1986 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Israel: Haifa General Information 1980-1985 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Israel: Haifa Miscellaneous Correspondence 1981-1985 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Israel: Haifa Publicity 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Austria: Vienna Student Orientation Handbook Spring 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Israel: Haifa Reports and Surveys 1980-1983 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Israel: Haifa Mancall Report 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Israel: Haifa Development Correspondence 1978-1986 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Israel: Haifa General 1983-1987 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - French Theme House Proposal 1975 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Italian Theme House Proposal (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Home Campus Faculty Teaching Overseas 1977-1979 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Mark Mancall Transnational Age Speech 10/1973 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Germany: Beutelsbach Photograph of Knorr Interns 1984 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Calendars 1981-1987 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Peru: Lima Handbooks 1982-1984 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Italy: Florence Calendars/Schedules 1978-1986 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Italy: Florence Field Trips 1978-1985 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Italy: Florence Gift Opportunities 1979-1985 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Italy: Florence General 1979-1989 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Italy: Florence Publicity (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Italy: Florence Student Orientation Handbook Winter 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Italy: Florence Videodisc Project 1986 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Italy: Florence Visitors to Stanford (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Italy: Florence Visitors to Italy: Florence (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Italy: Florence Curriculum 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Italy: Florence Course Proposals 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Italy: Florence Student Concerns 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Italy: Florence Student Concerns 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Course Proposals - Honoraria (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Applications by Major 1986 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - France: Paris Program History and Development 1981-1987 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Nigeria Program 1983-1985 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Africa Publicity (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Africa Administration General 1981-1984 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Egypt: Cairo Administration 1984 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Egypt: Cairo American University of Cairo Relations 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Egypt: Cairo Course Abstracts 1976-1981 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Egypt: Cairo Orientation 1984-1986 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Kenya: Nairobi Handbooks (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Togo Administration 1984 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Kenya: Nairobi Course Abstracts 1971-1980 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Kenya: Nairobi Orientation (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Peru: Lima Grade Equivalence 1986 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Peru: Lima Miscellaneous Correspondence 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Peru: Lima Course Abstracts 1979-1984 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Peru: Lima Applications/Selection 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Peru: Lima Course Lists 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Peru: Lima Applications/Selection 1984 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Peru: Lima Orientation 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Peru: Lima Orientation Correspondence 1979-1986 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Peru: Lima Transportation 1982-1985 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Peru: Lima Publicity (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Peru: Lima Student Finances 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Peru: Lima La Catolica Relations 1979-1986 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Peru: Lima SOCCIS 1977-1986 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Peru: Lima Director Selection 1978-1986 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Peru: Lima Program Budgets 1982-1984 (Box 5, Folder 16)